天啊  顾客全都裸体
Oh, my God, the customers are nakey.
幸好你也看得到
Thank God you're seeing it too.
我还以为我的透视眼能力又回来了呢
I thought my X-ray vision was back.
感谢每年一度的裸体单车骑行日
God bless the annual naked bike ride.
奥列格人呢
And where's Oleg?
这么多年来首次迎来午餐高峰期
This is the first lunch rush in years.
第三桌的那男的想要杯水
Uh, the guy at table three needs some water
他屁股上还有颗很需要人看的痣
and has an ass mole that should really get looked at,
可不该我看  该让医生看
but not by me.
奥列格  你也参加裸体单车骑行了吗
Oleg, you're doing the naked bike ride too?
你说裸体啥来着
The naked what?
好了  各位
Okay, gang.
继续上路吧
Let's hit the road.
我都不知道该看哪了
I don't know where to look now.
没有安全下眼的地方
Nothing's good.
这下这店真得烧掉消毒才行了
Well, now we have to burn this place down.
别想阻止我
Don't try and stop me.
我绝对会"汽"[水]死你
I'll Mountain Dew it.
我就是个可乐[卡]因上脑的神经病
You know I'm crazy when I'm all Coked up.
我昨晚听到了你房里传来不少"声响"呢
So I heard a lot of noise coming from your room last night.
我知道家里那只蝙蝠死了
And since I know that bat is dead,
因为它是心脏病发死在我枕头上
because it had a heart attack on my pillow,
所以我猜你昨晚带了一位绅士回家
I assume you had a gentleman caller?
他并不是一位绅士
He wasn't a gentleman,
不过我们打炮时  他的确戴了个单片眼镜
but he did wear a monocle while we did it.
你昨晚可比我"性奋"多了啊
Well, you had a much more exciting night than I did.
我的双腿在坐马桶上时"睡着"了
Both of my legs fell asleep on the toilet.
然后我也睡着了
Then so did I.
所以你们不会再见面了吗
So you aren't gonna see him again?
每次厄尔从我们身旁离开
Well, we know every time Earl walks away,
都有可能是最后一面
there's a chance of that.
我有件事宣布
I have an announcement.
那位老往我桌子涂花生酱的人
Whoever keeps putting peanut butter in my desk,
请住手
stop.
我对花生过敏
I'm allergic.
还有就是  我们这周日关店
And I'm closing the diner Sunday.
我们有过一段美好岁月
Well, we had a good run.
有你个大头鬼
No, we didn't.
大家来分赃啦
Let's scavenge, people!
各位再见
Bye, y'all!
店里的钱都收哪来着
Where do we keep the money at?
干嘛
What?
我可不想店里的肉类订货单
I don't want our meat order
落入不该落入的人手里
to fall into the wrong hands.
不是啦  你们这帮坏人
No, you pile of felons.
只是周日那一天不开门而已
I'm closing the diner for Sunday only.
反正这些东西我还是要据为己有
Well, I'm keeping this stuff anyway.
我好恨自己如此无下限
And I really hate it.
我的新心理医生盖里说
My new therapist, Gary, says that
我需要空出一天时间关注自身
I need to take a day off to focus on myself.
那他有给你个放大镜  让你先能看见自身吗
Did he give you a magnifying glass for that?
麦克斯  盖里说你用毒舌吐槽
Max, Gary says you use your toxic, mean-spirited jokes
来保持与我这种小天使的距离
to keep people like me at a distance.
你知道还能怎么跟你保持距离吗
You know what else works?
把我手抵在你脑门上就行
Putting my hand on your forehead.
麦克斯  盖里还说了
Max, Gary also says
你会如此恐惧与人亲近
you have a fear of intimacy
是源于小时候你爸爸抛弃你
stemming from your father abandoning you.
简单来说  就是你有恋父情节
To put it simply, you have daddy issues.
我唯一有的老爸刊物[恋父情节]
The only daddy issues I have
是汽车杂志
are of Rod Magazine.
而且世上才没有什么恋父情结
And there's no such thing as daddy issues.
如果有  那为什么我女儿会嫁给
If there was, why would my daughter be married
一个名叫二尔的健忘老头
to a forgetful older man named Burl?
阿憨  那盖里是怎么评价我
What did Gary say about me, Han?
有提到我宛如"伊莱莎·杜立德"吗
Were the words "Eliza Doolittle" used?
你的确是不干活儿[杜立德]
Well, you certainly do little,
不过其实并没有提到你
but actually, you didn't come up.
你也"没有"到我膝盖
You don't come up to my knees.
看到没  你得说出这样的东西
See? That's the kind of material you need
才会被人提到
to get a shout-out.
大家安安
Hey, everybody!
芭芭拉首次见到丑婴儿  并报以礼貌的微笑
Barbara just smiled politely at her first ugly baby.
我可以从她身上学点礼貌
Oh, I could learn some manners from her.
苏菲  说一个婴儿丑不太好吧
Sophie, it's really not nice to call a baby "Ugly."
闭上你狗嘴
Shut up!
我是说...
Oh, I mean...
闭嘴啦
Shut up!
苏菲  好消息
Good news, Sophie.
这周日我不用在这里跟另一家店上班啦
I don't have to work here or Bubzie's Hideaway this Sunday.
我们可以请个保姆看孩子
We can get a babysitter
就能过一天二人世界了
and spend the whole day together.
如果你是在暗示
Well, if you're suggesting
我们要再去赛狗场打炮
that we have sex at the dog track again,
那我的回答跟上次在赛狗场说的一样
then I'm gonna tell you what I said at the dog track.
这下所有人都该去看心理医生了
Well, now we all need therapy.
鲍比  太遗憾了
Oh, Bobby, I'm so sorry
你这周日得去你大姨的丧礼
you have to go to your great aunt's funeral on Sunday.
我真的很想去宜家吃午饭买毛巾呢
I really wanted to get lunch and some towels at Ikea.
如果你要去宜家
Ooh, if you're going to Ikea,
能帮我买个"思娜尔斯瓦顿卧根"吗
can you get me a snars-vaten-woggen?
我需要个地方放我的读书灯
I need a place to put my book light.
好啦  我理解
Okay, I understand.
从这件事上我们学到
I guess the real lesson is,
乘热气球时  千万别谎报体重
don't lie about your weight on a hot-air balloon.
我真的超超感到遗憾
I am so, so sorry...
我得听到你们这如此糟糕的通话
that I had to listen to that horrible phone conversation.
麦克斯  其实这是件好事
You know, Max, it's actually a good thing
鲍比阿姨如此悲剧死了
that Bobby's aunt died tragically.
这样我们周日就有空点货
Now we can do inventory here
还能多看几页手头的书
and get ahead on our books on Sunday.
只有你能把美好的死亡
Only you could turn a death
变成如此让人沮丧的事情
into something depressing.
说到令人沮丧的事物
Speaking of something depressing.
我就是过来跟你们说一声
I just came by to let you know
你们餐厅上班迟到了
you're late for the diner,
而且呢  麦克斯
and you know, Max,
我跟盖里共进了个工作早午餐
I had a working brunch with Gary,
他当时提出一个很棒的点
and he made a good point
就在他假装要买单时提的
as he pretended to reach for the check.
他说我那么做不对
He said it was unfair of me
我不应该说出你的问题
to bring up your problems
却又不提供解决方法
without offering a solution.
你需要去跟你父亲谈谈
You need to talk to your father.
阿憨  你这样真的太多管闲事了
Han, you are really overstepping your boundaries,
真是太没礼貌了  因为多管闲事是我的工作
which is really rude, because that's my job.
没关系
Uh, it's fine.
阿憨  那你去吧
Yeah, go ahead, Han.
加油把我爸找出来
Try and find my father.
我不知道他叫啥  住在哪
I don't know his name, where he lives,
或在哪里做肾透析  我估计他会需要
or where he gets dialysis, I'm assuming.
想找他  我祝你好运
So good luck with that.
这是他的名字跟电话
Here's his name and number.
他住在罗德岛州
He lives in Rhode Island,
全美最无聊的州
America's least exciting state.
你怎么查出来的
How did you find that?
这也多管闲事过头了
That is way over the line,
我好希望是我做出这样的事啊
and I really wish it was me who had done it.
这跟麦克斯读高中时不一样
Unlike Max in high school,
不是"随便"就行
it wasn't easy.
我打去医院问她出生证明
I called the hospital for her birth certificate,
医院让我去档案室
which led me to the hall of records,
结果在档案室  我被逼着和一位
which then led me to some forced necking
名为谢莉的办事员耳鬓厮磨
with a clerk named Shelley.
可惜  最后一无所获
Sadly, it was a dead end.
所以最后是盖里帮我搞到的
So Gary got it for me.
他妹妹是跟警察合作的灵媒
His sister's a psychic for the police.
所以你要打电话给你父亲吗
So are you gonna call your dad
看在我和阿憨如此辛苦地给你弄来他的号码
after all that hard work Han and I did to find his number.
我也不知道
I don't know.
这是一个重大决定
This is a huge decision,
我想要好好考虑后再做决定
and I really want to think this through.
麦克斯  我觉得你这么做很聪明很成...
Max, I think that's a really smart and mature decis...
考虑完了
Thought about it.
我们少了两瓶龙舌兰酒
Okay, we're missing two bottles of tequila,
但我找到了一把带血的刀
but I did find a bloody knife,
所以点货就到此为止吧
so that's a wrap on inventory.
谢天谢地
Oh, thank God.
这种纸上工作真是让我想自杀
I've been killing myself with all this paperwork.
我花了足足三十分钟折出这顶帽子呢
It took me 30 minutes to make this hat.
麦克斯  我看出你在干嘛了
Max, I know what's really going on here.
你想通过折纸来掩饰自己
You're trying to hide it by doing origami,
但其实你心里正想着要不要联系你爸爸
but you're really thinking about contacting your dad.
其实我刚真正在想
Uh, actually, I was thinking
我那把带血的刀放哪去了
about where I left my bloody knife,
不过你刚才已经为我解疑
but you solved that mystery.
所以现在我在想着摔跤
So now I'm thinking about wrestling.
跟你的内心情感摔跤搏斗吗
Wrestling with your emotions?
不是  是跟演员杰瑞米·皮文
No, with Jeremy Piven.
他手臂短  我能打赢他
Short arms. I can take him.
我怕你哪天好死不死你想打给你爸爸
Well, in the off-chance you do want to contact your father,
所以我用我强大的拼图技巧
I used my amazing jigsaw puzzle talents
把号码拼回去了
to put his number back together.
我可是2003年拼图大赛的亚军
I was runner-up in Jigsaw Palooza 2003.
太谢谢你了
Oh, thank God.
感谢你  卡洛琳
Thank you, Caroline...
让我有机会再把它撕成渣
for letting me rip this up again.
你知道吗  我也不想这么说
You know, I hate to say this,
但阿憨这次真的没错
but Han's not wrong.
你好大的狗胆
How dare you?
先听我说完
Let me finish.
或许你真的在与人亲近方面有问题
Maybe you do have some intimacy issues.
毕竟你跟兰迪分手后  就没再谈过恋爱
I mean, you haven't really dated anyone since Randy,
而且你到现在还没有给我咱们家的钥匙
and I still don't have a key to our apartment.
我给了你一把螺丝刀  那个也能开啊
I gave you that screwdriver. It works.
你难道就没有一点点想见他的好奇心吗
You're not even a little curious to meet him?
或许有一点吧
I guess maybe a little.
或许见完之后  我身上一些古怪的地方就能说得通了
Maybe it'll explain some of the more disturbing things about me,
比如我喜欢巧克力早餐片多过水果早餐片
like how I prefer Cocoa Pebbles over Fruity Pebbles.
对啊  你终于能知道原因了
Yes! You can finally get those answers.
我觉得我们立刻出发  免得你又改变主意
I say we go now, before you change your mind.
我们该从餐厅偷点零食
Should we steal some snacks from the diner
再去偷阿憨的车吗
before we steal Han's car?
厄尔  你在这里干嘛
Earl, what are you doing here?
你知道今天不用上班的吧
You know you're off today, right?
我把我的大麻忘在这里了
Uh, I forgot my weed here.
然后我抽掉了
Then I smoked it.
所以现在我在哪已经无所谓了
And now it doesn't matter where I am.
我有照盖里吩咐的做  我不是来上班的
I'm not working on my Gary-prescribed day off.
我只是顺道来这里...  见个朋友
I just swung by to... to meet a friend...
他叫贾鹏友
named Friendo.
他是真的
He's Italian.
你们来这里干嘛
What are you doing here?
我们要去见麦克斯的父亲
We're going to meet Max's dad.
是我说服了她
Because of me.
现在这是我的招牌了
It's my thing now.
所以你要放弃你其他招牌了吗
So you're giving up your other thing?
比如让客人在一旁饿肚子  而你忙着自吹自擂
Complimenting yourself while the customers starve?
厄尔  你要不要一起来
Earl, why don't you come with?
我想我的生父见我的养父
I want my real dad to meet my birth dad.
行啊  我是哪个身份来着
Sure. Which one am I again?
我能一起来吗
Can I come too?
盖里一定会很想了解
Gary would love to hear about the man
造成我惨况的人
responsible for my misery.
造成你惨况的不是擦除你一半身躯的漫画家吗
Isn't that the cartoonist who erased half your body?
这下好了
Ugh, great.
让别的洗劫者抢先了
Other looters got here first.
谁让你在去抢零食的路上
This is what happens when you stop for snacks
还浪费时间去买零食啊
on your way to stop for more snacks.
我们要来一趟乡间浪漫自驾游
We're going for a romantic ride in the country.
我们想找一个能啪啪啪的农场
We're looking for a farm where we can do it.
我们准备叫阿憨开车载我们去罗德岛
We were just gonna ask Han to drive us to Rhode Island,
不过这样更好
but this is better.
坐你们的休旅车
With your minivan,
我们就能坐得离驾驶员更远了
we can sit much further from the driver.
罗德岛吗
Rhode Island?
我们是要去埋尸体吗
Are we gonna bury a dead body?
不是  但我会跟去
No, but I am coming,
所以不许动歪脑筋
so don't get any ideas.
我上一次跟一堆怪人同坐休旅车
Well, I haven't been in a van with this many weirdos
还是我第二次被绑架那会儿呢
since the second time I got kidnapped.
你父亲刚确认了
All right, your dad just confirmed.
他会4点钟在罗德岛餐厅跟我们碰面
We're meeting him at 4:00 at the Rhode Island Diner.
麦克斯与父亲重逢的事  打从我接管过来后
Max's reunion with her father is really humming along
就开始拨云见日  水到渠成
since I took the reins from Han.
你别自己骗自己了
Don't kid yourself.
是我搞定了良好基础
I laid the groundwork.
你才别自己骗自己了
Don't kid yourself.
你这辈子啥都没"搞"过
You've never laid anything.
奥列格  我们下个出口就该下了吧
Oleg, shouldn't we be getting off at the next exit?
你觉得我们该在33B出口下吗  咪湿蒂
Do you think we should exit at 33B, Misty?
下个出口施工关闭了  小色魔
Ooh, that exit is closed for construction, naughty boy.
由于今天芭芭拉不会在
Since we're having a day off from Barbara,
我把导航设置为成人模式了
I put the GPS on XXX.
女人就不能只是正常跟你说话吗
Can't a woman just talk to you?
这就是为什么女人要游行示威
This is why we march.
要不要来玩个有趣的汽车游戏
How about a fun car game?
猜猜我的间谍小眼睛
I spy with my little eye
看到了什么黑色的东西
something that is black.
臭小子  你他妈找死啊
You better watch yourself, son.
不是  刚才我的谜底是...
No, I was referring to...
算了  过
pass.
麦克斯  你紧张吗
Max, are you nervous?
你脸上又浮现了跟当时你发现
You have that nervous metallic smell you get
便利店热狗卖完时一样的紧张僵硬笑容
when you find out 7-Eleven's out of hot dogs.
才没有
No.
只是裤兜里放了很多硬币不舒服而已
I keep a lot of nickels in these pants.
苏菲你还好吧
Sophie, are you okay?
还好啊  我起床都这样
Yeah, that's just how I wake up.
你才还好吧
Are you okay?
下个出口向右
Bear right at the next exit.
就是那样
Just like that.
不要停
Don't stop!
好的  咪湿蒂
Okay, Misty.
你导航的配音员好像是我美发学校同学
I think I went to hair school with your GPS.
前方有物体
Object ahead.
慢点  大公鸡哥哥
Slow down, big boy.
我撞到了只松鼠
Uh-oh, I hit a squirrel
或者是约翰·特拉沃尔塔的假发
or John Travolta's toupee.
无论是啥  它的脚还在动呢
Either way, its legs are still moving.
天啊
Oh, gosh.
我刚才好像又睡着了
I must have fallen asleep again.
阿憨
Hey, Han?
松鼠语的"撑着点"怎么说
How do you say "Hang in there" in squirrel?
我从儿童动物节目学的
I learned it on Zoboomafoo.
苏菲  下次你用甜甜圈盒
Sophie, next time you scoop up
捞起一只受伤动物时
a wounded animal with a donut box,
能先确保大家都吃过了好吗
make sure everyone's had one first.
他正舒服躺在一个油炸煎饼上
Aww, he's resting comfortably on a cruller.
过着我梦想中的生活啊  兄弟
Living my dream, buddy.
他不会死吧
He won't die, right?
在乌克兰杀松鼠是犯法的
It's illegal to kill squirrels in the Ukraine.
因为普京把它们都训练成间谍了
Ever since Putin had them trained as spies.
附近有一家宠物医院
There's an animal hospital nearby.
把地址输入进性感导航吧
Put the address in the sexy GPS lady.
我们去哪我不在意
I don't care where we go,
我只想听当我们"到达目的"时
I just want to hear what she does
她会作何"反应"
when we arrive at our destination.
我不想当扫兴的人
Not to be that person,
但现在我才是管事的
but I'm in charge now,
而这趟旅程麦克斯跟爸爸重逢才是关键
and this trip is about Max meeting her dad,
不是拯救松鼠大作战
not saving a squirrel's life.
仇松鼠者
Squirrel hater!
就带着他跟我们一起去嘛
Let's just take him with us.
如果这家餐厅像我们那家
If this diner's anything like ours,
那里面就会有无数啮齿动物能陪他玩了
there'd be tons of other rodents for him to play with.
距离目的地还有12192公分
Your destination is in 4,800 inches.
我让她把距离换成公分
I had her convert everything to inches.
现在旅途是不是听起来又大又长啊
Makes our trip sound bigger, doesn't it?
我们应该计划游行抗议了
We should plan a march.
要一个...
Table for, uh...
二人桌
for two.
然后"美国恐怖故事:面包车"的演员们
And the cast of American Horror Story: Minivan
坐在另一桌
will be in a separate booth.
不介意我吃一个吧
Ooh, do you mind?
我挺饿
I'm pretty hungry.
我的甜甜圈上沾满了松鼠口水
My donut is covered in squirrel slobber.
本店不能带外食入内
You can't bring outside food in here.
这不是食物
It's not food.
里面是一只严重受伤的松鼠
It's a severely injured squirrel.
好吧  你们随便坐
All right, well, sit wherever.
别让他跑出盒外就行了
Just don't let it out of the box.
你看到没  厄尔
Do you see that, Earl?
他立场坚定  讲道理
He's firm but fair.
你看起来像年轻的厄尔
You look like a young Earl.
不是  我叫史蒂夫
No, I'm Steve.
那是厄尔年轻时的名字
That was young Earl's name!
大家安安
Hey, everybody!
我就这么弱气入场吧
Uh, I'm just going in.
我跟你父亲说找金发正妹就对了
I told your dad to look for a pretty blonde girl
头发比短发长
whose hair is a little longer than a bob
但是又还没长过肩
but shorter than shoulder-length.
我忘了告诉他你长什么样了
Oh, I forgot to tell him what you look like.
我也不知道他长什么样啊
Well, I have no idea what he looks like.
我一直想象他像路易斯CK  但是又没他帅
I always imagined Louis CK, but not as hot.
或许你真有恋父情节
Maybe you do have daddy issues.
往好处看  至少我们永远不会爱上同个男人
On the plus side, we will never like the same guy.
盖里说当麦克斯看到她父亲
Gary says when Max sees her dad,
她会变得非常情绪化
she's going to get very emotional.
有可能是大喜
She could get happy,
然后大悲
then sad.
反正就是藏好叉子之类的凶器
Basically, hide your forks.
他又尿了
He peed again.
天啊
Oh, Lord,
我又尿失禁了吗
am I peeing?
这条可是我最好的裤子了
But these are my best pants.
他尿这么多  甜甜圈盒都变成泳池了
He peed so much, he turned this donut box into a pool.
油炸煎饼被他弄成"哎油"煎饼
He's really putting the "Ew" in cruller.
麦克斯  如果你父亲来了你需要保留隐私
Max, if you want privacy when your dad gets here,
我可以去坐在别桌
I can go sit in that other booth.
那你能现在就去吗
Can you do that now?
有精神点  各位
Look alive, everyone!
我们期待许久的时刻终于到来了
It's the moment we've always been waiting for.
至少是从周二盖里建议过后开始期待
At least since Tuesday, since Gary suggested it.
然后我接手了
Then I took over.
麦克斯  抱他的时候记得看我这边
Max, make sure you look at me when you hug him.
那个男的吗  希望不要啊
Oh, that guy? I hope not.
别是我爸  别是我爸  别是我爸
No daddy, no daddy, no daddy.
他有哪里不好
What was wrong with him?
你是说除了他的牛仔裤
Besides his jeans,
手臂  腿  脸  和气质吗
arms, legs, face, and overall vibe?
你知道爱上自己老爸是坏事的吧
You know it would be bad if you were attracted to him, right?
你知道吗  我在你这个年纪时也是收银员
You know, I was a cashier when I was your age.
是吗  那你现在做什么工作
Yeah? What do you do now?
收银员
Cashier.
-这份工作只是暂时的  -暂时的
- But this is just temporary. - Temporary.
-我可是有梦想的  -梦想的
- No, I have actual dreams. - Dreams.
不是  我是认真的
No, seriously, man.
-我吹萨克斯风  -萨克斯风
- I play saxophone. - Saxophone.
我辞职
I quit.
真乖
Attaboy.
你知道吗  阿憨
You know, Han,
你应该让你店里的厨子也搞这种煎饼出来
you should get your chef to make flapjacks like this.
他自己就做了够多"搞"与"奸"了
He does enough flapping and jacking on his own.
我觉得松鼠好像睡着了
I think this squirrel's asleep.
他一边打呼  一边握着自己蛋蛋
He's snoring and clutching his nuts.
就跟你睡觉时一样
Aww, just like you do.
阿憨  你能帮忙照看松鼠
Han, will you watch the squirrel
让我跟苏菲有一会儿独处时间吗
so we can just have one minute to ourselves?
不行  我在顾着门  等着麦克斯的...
No, I'm watching the door for Max's...
我该怎么说好听点呢
how do I put this nicely?
"在她小时候就抛弃她的魔鬼"
"Monster who left her as a child."
他会来的
He's gonna be here.
我为什么这么乐观啊
Why am I so positive?
我唯一知道自己爹在哪里的原因
The only reason I know where my dad is
是因为他在坐牢
is 'cause he's in prison.
有个新鲜的进来啦
Ooh, live one coming in.
这家伙感觉就不是个顾家爱孩子的人
This guy looks like he's missed a few soccer games.
如果那个废柴是我爸  就说我没来
If that jabroni is him, tell him I'm not here.
麦克斯  其中一个废柴
Max, one of these losers
将会是你老爸
is gonna be your dad.
毕竟这里可是罗德岛
I mean, we're in Rhode Island.
我去续杯
I'm gonna get a quick refill.
没事的  姐妹  咱们是同行
I got it, hon. I'm in the industry.
卡洛琳  我开始觉得他不会来了
Caroline, I'm starting to think he's not going to show.
你这次真是彻底搞砸了
You really screwed the pooch this time.
我吗
Me?
对啊  这事不是你接手了吗
Yeah, this is your thing now.
你不是说从我那里接手过去了吗
You took the reins, remember?
你就是特雷弗·诺亚
You're Trevor Noah,
而我是囧司徒
and I'm Jon Stewart.
我已经得了艾美奖
I've got my Emmys.
我光荣退位了
I'm done now.
是你起的头
Well, you started this.
在我好不容易帮助她走出兰迪的事之后
And after I finally got her over Randy.
她好不容易才不再夜惊[魔王]呢
The night terrors just stopped.
我之前一到晚上可怕她了
I was terrified of her at night.
你现在自己晚上带着便宜电击棒睡吧
You can sleep with a cheap Taser now.
我已经是这样了啊
I already do.
也是因为怕她啊
For the same reason!
安静
Quiet!
松鼠在睡觉
The squirrel is sleeping.
我们好不容易把他哄睡
We just got him down.
而且我们想开始亲热了
And we'd like to make out.
我洒了很多糖浆到自己身上
I spilled a lot of syrup on myself.
咱们就叫醒厄尔然后走人吧
Let's just wake Earl up and get out of here.
我爸不会来的
My dad's not coming.
或许你爸还在路上呢
Maybe your dad's still on his way.
我听说高速公路上在堵车
I heard traffic's building up on all the expressways.
其实这还挺讽刺的对吧
Kind of an ironic name, wouldn't you say?
还"高速"公路呢
"Expressway"?
应该是"慢速"公路吧
More like "Slow-way."
这事反正归卡洛琳管了
This is Caroline's thing.
走吧
Let's just go.
肉桂卷甜品店不留隔夜货  我想赶回去捡免费的
I want to get back before Cinnabon gives away their day-olds.
你知道我们现在是甜品店老板吧
You know we own a dessert bar, right?
或许他还在来的路上呢
Maybe he's still gonna come.
我唯一知道这个我不认识的男人的一件事
If I know one thing about the man I know nothing about,
就是他不会来
he is not coming.
你失望了吗
Are you disappointed?
没有
No.
有一点吧
A little.
但或许他不来更好吧
But maybe it's for the best he didn't come.
这就是我不想见他的原因
This is why I didn't want to meet him,
因为无论是谁从那门走进来
because whoever comes through that door
都只会让我感到失望
is just gonna disappoint me.
他没来  好歹我可以幻想他是个很屌的人
And this way, I get to imagine he's someone cool,
比如布特·雷诺茨
like Burt Reynolds
或者是脆脆上校
or Captain Crunch.
所以你真的没事吗
So you're really okay?
对啊
Yeah.
我们过了很开心的一天
We had a great day.
自驾游  见到一只很酷的松鼠
Road trip, met a cool squirrel.
我的生命里不缺这么一个废柴
I don't need another loser in my life.
我有你们就够了
I have you guys.
盖里
Gary!
麦克斯的父亲没来
Max's father didn't show.
我有什么感觉吗
How does that make me feel?
很糟糕啊
Terrible!
我感觉阿憨接受程度没我好啊
I don't think Han's handling it as well as I am.
说实话  这事要是归我管
Honestly, if it were my thing,
我现在一定会超想自尽谢罪
I would want to kill myself right now.
她内心受伤了  她是我的家人
She's hurt, and she's family to me.
这让我有啥感觉吗
How does that make me feel?
我当时不应该找医保能报销的便宜医生
Like I should have gone to an out-of-network doctor!
天啊  我在休息日也让阿憨崩溃了呢
God, I made Han have a meltdown on my day off.
你才冷静  盖里
You calm down, Gary!
我才不要数到十
I won't count to ten.
你他妈自己数到十  你个傻逼
You count to ten, you bastard!
欢迎光临...
Hey, welcome to the, uh...
这家店叫什么鬼来着
hey, uh, what the hell is this place called, anyway?
天啊
Oh, my God.
老爸
Dad!
等等  盖里
Hold on, Gary.
有个很可能是麦克斯父亲的游民走进来了
A vagrant that could very well be Max's father just walked in.
假装你是我爸  我就给你40块
Pretend you're my dad, and I'll give you 40 bucks.
再加一只大麻烟  咱们就成交
Throw in a joint, and we have a deal.
或许你真是我爸
Maybe you are my dad.
没有  我才没有孩子
Oh, no, I don't have kids.
吸太多大麻了
Too much pot.
各位  这位是我爸
Guys, this is my dad.
我是这位辣妹的爸爸
I'm the hot girl's dad.
有人跟我一样期待她爸是警察吗
Was anyone else expecting a cop?
你们懂  显得更讽刺
I mean, you know, for the irony.
我叫卡洛琳
I'm Caroline.
你看  就像我说的  不是短发
See, it's, like, not a bob,
但也还没长过肩
but it's not shoulder-length.
这场父女重聚由我一手策划
I'm responsible for this reunion.
其实他不是我爸
Um, he's not really my dad.
我就是安慰一下阿憨
I'm doing this for Han.
好啦  各位
All right, everybody.
我爸跟我进行了一场感天动地的重聚
Uh, my dad and I have had be Max's father just walked in.
现在他得去执行秘密任务了
and now he has to get to a secret mission.
在异国的某处
In an exotic locale.
当然啦
Sure.
我被规定不能离开这个郡
But I can't leave the county.
当然啦  当地秘密任务
Sure. Local secret mission.
你感觉是个好孩子
Hey, you seem like a nice kid.
你的父亲应该以你为荣
Your father should be proud.
谢谢
Thanks.
盖里  抱歉我刚才一时爆发
Sorry about the outburst, Gary.
你也知道这问题起源于我妈对我期望过高
You know it stems from my mother's expectations.
谢谢你为我做的这些  阿憨
Thanks for doing this, Han.
有人想来大抱一个吗
Anyone in the hug business?
我都没被吓到
I didn't even flinch.
咱们真的有进步啊
We are making progress.
你跟来吗  厄尔
You coming, Earl?
当然啦
Sure am.
我可不想一辈子都困在收银员这位置上
Don't want to get stuck being a cashier my whole life.
奥列格  你忘了那只松鼠啦
Oleg, you forgot the damn squirrel.
走吧  小伙子
Come on, little guy.
我们不会丢下任何一个人
We don't abandon anybody.